Inside Albany Records
Inside Albany Records
- Videorecordings
  - Videorecordings, 1995
    - No. 2202, 1995-06-24; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0748 (Box 78)
    - No. 2203, 1995-07-01; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0748 (Box 78)
    - No. 2204, 1995-07-08; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0748 (Box 78)
    - No. 2205, 1995-07-15; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0749 (Box 65)
    - No. 2206, 1995-07-22; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0749 (Box 65)
    - No. 2207, 1995-07-29; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0749 (Box 65)
  - Videorecordings, 1996
    - No. 9601, 1996-01-05; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0341 (Box 36)
    - No. 9602, 1996-01-12; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0341 (Box 36)
    - No. 9603, 1996-01-19; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0341 (Box 36)
    - No. 9604, 1996-01-26; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0342 (Box 36)
    - No. 9605, 1996-02-02; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0342 (Box 36)
    - No. 9606, 1996-02-09; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0342 (Box 36)
    - No. 9607, 1996-02-17; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0343 (Box 36)
    - No. 9608, 1996-02-24; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0343 (Box 36)
    - No. 9609, 1996-03-02; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0343 (Box 36)
    - No. 9610, 1996-03-08; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0344 (Box 36)
    - No. 9611, 1996-03-15; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0344 (Box 36)
    - No. 9612, 1996-03-22; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0344 (Box 36)
    - No. 9613, 1996-03-30; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0345 (Box 36)
    - No. 9614, 1996-04-06; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0345 (Box 36)
    - No. 9615, 1996-04-13; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0345 (Box 36)
    - No. 9616, 1996-04-19; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0346 (Box 36)
    - No. 9617, 1996-04-26; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0346 (Box 36)
    - No. 9618, 1996-05-03; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0346 (Box 36)
    - No. 9619, 1996-05-10; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0347 (Box 36)
    - No. 9620, 1996-05-17; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0347 (Box 36)
    - No. 9621, 1996-05-24; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0347 (Box 36)
    - No. 9622, 1996-05-31; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0348 (Box 36)
    - No. 9623, 1996-06-07; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0348 (Box 36)
    - No. 9624, 1996-06-14; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0348 (Box 36)
    - No. 9625, 1996-06-21; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0349 (Box 36)
    - No. 9626, 1996-06-28; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0349 (Box 36)
    - No. 9627, 1996-07-05; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0349 (Box 36)
    - No. 9628, 1996-07-12; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0350 (Box 37)
    - No. 9629, 1996-07-20; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0350 (Box 37)
    - No. 9630, 1996-07-26; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0350 (Box 37)
    - No. 9631, 1996-08-02; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0351 (Box 37)
    - No. 9632, 1996-08-09; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0351 (Box 37)
    - No. 9633, 1996-08-16; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0351 (Box 37)
    - No. 9634, 1996-08-23; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0352 (Box 37)
    - No. 9635, 1996-08-30; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0352 (Box 37)
    - No. 9636, 1996-09-06; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0352 (Box 37)
    - No. 9637, 1996-09-13; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0353 (Box 37)
    - No. 9638, 1996-09-20; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0353 (Box 37)
    - No. 9639, 1996-09-27; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0353 (Box 37)
    - No. 9640, 1996-10-04; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0354 (Box 37)
    - No. 9641, 1996-10-11; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0354 (Box 37)
    - No. 9642, 1996-10-18; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0354 (Box 37)
    - No. 9643, 1996-10-25; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0355 (Box 37)
    - No. 9644, 1996-11-01; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0355 (Box 37)
    - No. 9645, 1996-11-08; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0355 (Box 37)
    - No. 9646, 1996-11-15; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0356 (Box 37)
    - No. 9647, 1996-11-22; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0356 (Box 37)
    - No. 9648, 1996-11-29; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0356 (Box 37)
    - No. 9649, 1996-12-07; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0357 (Box 37)
    - No. 9650, 1996-12-14; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0357 (Box 37)
    - No. 9651, 1996-12-21; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0357 (Box 37)
    - No. 9652, 1996-12-27; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0358 (Box 37)
  - Videorecordings, 1997
    - No. 9701, 1997-01-03; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0358 (Box 37)
    - No. 9702, 1997-01-14; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0358 (Box 37)
    - No. 9703, 1997-01-17; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0359 (Box 37)
    - No. 9704, 1997-01-24; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0359 (Box 37)
    - No. 9705, 1997-01-31; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0359 (Box 37)
    - No. 9706, 1997-02-07; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0360 (Box 37)
    - No. 9707, 1997-02-14; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0360 (Box 37)
    - No. 9708, 1997-02-21; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0360 (Box 37)
    - No. 9709, 1997-02-28; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0361 (Box 37)
    - No. 9710, 1997-03-07; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0361 (Box 37)
    - No. 9711, 1997-03-14; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0361 (Box 37)
    - No. 9712, 1997-03-21; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0362 (Box 38)
    - No. 9713, 1997-03-28; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0362 (Box 38)
    - No. 9714, 1997-04-04; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0362 (Box 38)
    - No. 9715, 1997-04-11; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0363 (Box 38)
    - No. 9716, 1997-04-18; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0363 (Box 38)
    - No. 9717, 1997-04-25; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0363 (Box 38)
    - No. 9718, 1997-05-02; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0364 (Box 38)
    - No. 9719, 1997-05-09; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0364 (Box 38)
    - No. 9720, 1997-05-16; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0364 (Box 38)
    - No. 9721, 1997-05-24; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0365 (Box 38)
    - No. 9722, 1997-05-31; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0365 (Box 38)
    - No. 9723, 1997-06-07; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0365 (Box 38)
    - No. 9724, 1997-06-13; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0366 (Box 38)
    - No. 9725, 1997-06-20; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0366 (Box 38)
    - No. 9726, 1997-06-27; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0366 (Box 38)
    - No. 9727, 1997-07-03; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0367 (Box 38)
    - No. 9728, 1997-07-11; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0367 (Box 38)
    - No. 9729, 1997-07-18; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0367 (Box 38)
    - No. 9730, 1997-07-25; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0368 (Box 38)
    - No. 9731, 1997-08-01; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0368 (Box 38)
    - No. 9732, 1997-08-08; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0368 (Box 38)
    - No. 9733, 1997-08-15; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0369 (Box 38)
    - No. 9734, 1997-08-22; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0369 (Box 38)
    - No. 9735, 1997-08-29; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0369 (Box 38)
    - No. 9736, 1997-09-05; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0370 (Box 38)
    - No. 9737, 1997-09-12; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0370 (Box 38)
    - No. 9738, 1997-09-19; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0370 (Box 38)
    - No. 9739, 1997-09-27; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0371 (Box 38)
    - No. 9740, 1997-10-04; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0371 (Box 38)
    - No. 9741, 1997-10-11; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0371 (Box 38)
    - No. 9742, 1997-10-17; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0372 (Box 38)
    - No. 9743, 1997-10-24; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0372 (Box 38)
    - No. 9744, 1997-10-31; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0372 (Box 38)
    - No. 9745, 1997-11-08; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0373 (Box 38)
    - No. 9746, 1997-11-15; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0373 (Box 38)
    - No. 9747, 1997-11-22; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0373 (Box 38)
    - No. 9748, 1997-11-28; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0374 (Box 39)
    - No. 9749, 1997-12-05; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0374 (Box 39)
    - No. 9750, 1997-12-12; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0374 (Box 39)
    - No. 9751, 1997-12-19; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0375 (Box 39)
    - No. 9752, 1997-12-26; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0375 (Box 39)
  - Videorecordings, 1998
    - No. 9801, 1998-01-02; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0375 (Box 39)
    - No. 9802, 1998-01-09; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0376 (Box 39)
    - No. 9803, 1998-01-16; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0376 (Box 39)
    - No. 9804, 1998-01-23; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0376 (Box 39)
    - No. 9805, 1998-01-30; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0377 (Box 39)
    - No. 9806, 1998-02-06; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0377 (Box 39)
    - No. 9807, 1998-02-13; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0377 (Box 39)
    - No. 9808, 1998-02-20; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0378 (Box 39)
    - No. 9809, 1998-02-28; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0378 (Box 39)
    - No. 9810, 1998-03-06; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0378 (Box 39)
    - No. 9811, 1998-03-13; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0379 (Box 39)
    - No. 9812, 1998-03-20; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0379 (Box 39)
    - No. 9813, 1998-03-27; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0379 (Box 39)
    - No. 9814, 1998-04-03; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0380 (Box 39)
    - No. 9815, 1998-04-10; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0380 (Box 39)
    - No. 9816, 1998-04-17; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0380 (Box 39)
    - No. 9817, 1998-04-24; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0381 (Box 39)
    - No. 9818, 1998-05-01; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0381 (Box 39)
    - No. 9819, 1998-05-08; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0381 (Box 39)
    - No. 9820, 1998-05-15; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0382 (Box 39)
    - No. 9821, 1998-05-22; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0382 (Box 39)
    - No. 9822, 1998-05-29; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0382 (Box 39)
    - No. 9823, 1998-06-05; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0383 (Box 39)
    - No. 9824, 1998-06-12; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0383 (Box 39)
    - No. 9825, 1998-06-19; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0383 (Box 39)
    - No. 9826, 1998-06-27; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0384 (Box 39)
    - No. 9827, 1998-07-04; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0384 (Box 39)
    - No. 9828, 1998-07-11; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0384 (Box 39)
    - No. 9829, 1998-07-18; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0385 (Box 39)
    - No. 9830, 1998-07-25; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0385 (Box 39)
    - No. 9831, 1998-08-01; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0385 (Box 39)
    - No. 9832, 1998-08-07; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0386 (Box 40)
    - No. 9833, 1998-08-14; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0386 (Box 40)
    - No. 9834, 1998-08-21; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0386 (Box 40)
    - No. 9835, 1998-08-28; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0387 (Box 40)
    - No. 9836, 1998-09-04; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0387 (Box 40)
    - No. 9837, 1998-09-11; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0387 (Box 40)
    - No. 9838, 1998-09-18; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0388 (Box 40)
    - No. 9839, 1998-09-25; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0388 (Box 40)
    - No. 9840, 1998-10-02; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0388 (Box 40)
    - No. 9841, 1998-10-09; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0389 (Box 40)
    - No. 9842, 1998-10-16; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0389 (Box 40)
    - No. 9843, 1998-10-23; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0389 (Box 40)
    - No. 9844, 1998-10-30; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0390 (Box 40)
    - No. 9845, 1998-11-06; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0390 (Box 40)
    - No. 9846, 1998-11-13; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0390 (Box 40)
    - No. 9847, 1998-11-20; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0391 (Box 40)
    - No. 9848, 1998-11-27; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0391 (Box 40)
    - No. 9849, 1998-12-04; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0391 (Box 40)
    - No. 9850, 1998-12-11; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0392 (Box 40)
    - No. 9851, 1998-12-18; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0392 (Box 40)
    - No. 9852, 1998-12-25; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0392 (Box 40)
  - Videorecordings, 1999
    - No. 9901, 1999-01-01; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0393 (Box 40)
    - No. 9902, 1999-01-08; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0393 (Box 40)
    - No. 9903, 1999-01-15; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0393 (Box 40)
    - No. 9904, 1999-01-22; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0394 (Box 40)
    - No. 9905, 1999-01-29; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0394 (Box 40)
    - No. 9906, 1999-02-05; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0394 (Box 40)
    - No. 9907, 1999-02-12; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0395 (Box 40)
    - No. 9908, 1999-02-19; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0395 (Box 40)
    - No. 9909, 1999-02-26; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0395 (Box 40)
    - No. 9910, 1999-03-05; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0396 (Box 40)
    - No. 9911, 1999-03-12; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0396 (Box 40)
    - No. 9912, 1999-03-19; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0396 (Box 40)
    - No. 9913, 1999-03-26; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0397 (Box 40)
    - No. 9914, 1999-04-02; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0397 (Box 40)
    - No. 9915, 1999-04-09; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0397 (Box 40)
    - No. 9916, 1999-04-16; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0398 (Box 40)
    - No. 9917, 1999-04-23; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0398 (Box 40)
    - No. 9918, 1999-04-30; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0398 (Box 40)
    - No. 9919, 1999-05-07; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0399 (Box 41)
    - No. 9920, 1999-05-14; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0399 (Box 41)
    - No. 9921, 1999-05-21; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0399 (Box 41)
    - No. 9922, 1999-05-28; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0400 (Box 41)
    - No. 9923, 1999-06-04; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0400 (Box 41)
    - No. 9924, 1999-06-11; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0400 (Box 41)
    - No. 9925, 1999-06-18; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0401 (Box 41)
    - No. 9926, 1999-06-25; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0401 (Box 41)
    - No. 9927, 1999-07-02; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0401 (Box 41)
    - No. 9928, 1999-07-09; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0402 (Box 41)
    - No. 9929, 1999-07-16; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0402 (Box 41)
    - No. 9930, 1999-07-23; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0402 (Box 41)
    - No. 9931, 1999-07-30; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0403 (Box 41)
    - No. 9932, 1999-08-06; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0403 (Box 41)
    - No. 9933, 1999-08-13; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0403 (Box 41)
    - No. 9934, 1999-08-20; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0404 (Box 41)
    - No. 9935, 1999-08-27; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0404 (Box 41)
    - No. 9936, 1999-09-03; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0404 (Box 41)
    - No. 9937, 1999-09-10; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0405 (Box 41)
    - No. 9938, 1999-09-17; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0405 (Box 41)
    - No. 9939, 1999-09-24; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0405 (Box 41)
    - No. 9940, 1999-10-01; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0406 (Box 41)
    - No. 9941, 1999-10-08; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0406 (Box 41)
    - No. 9942, 1999-10-15; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0406 (Box 41)
    - No. 9943, 1999-10-22; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0407 (Box 41)
    - No. 9944, 1999-10-29; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0407 (Box 41)
    - No. 9945, 1999-11-05; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0407 (Box 41)
    - No. 9946, 1999-11-12; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0408 (Box 41)
    - No. 9947, 1999-11-19; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0408 (Box 41)
    - No. 9948, 1999-11-26; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0408 (Box 41)
    - No. 9949, 1999-12-03; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0409 (Box 41)
    - No. 9950, 1999-12-10; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0409 (Box 41)
    - No. 9951, 1999-12-17; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0409 (Box 41)
    - No. 9952, 1999-12-24; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0410 (Box 41)
  - Videorecordings, 2000
    - No. 0001, 2000-01-01; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0410 (Box 41)
    - No. 0002, 2000-01-07; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0410 (Box 41)
    - No. 0003, 2000-01-14; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0411 (Box 41)
    - No. 0004, 2000-01-21; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0411 (Box 41)
    - No. 0005, 2000-01-28; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0411 (Box 41)
    - No. 0006, 2000-02-04; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0412 (Box 42)
    - No. 0007, 2000-02-11; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0412 (Box 42)
    - No. 0008, 2000-02-18; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0412 (Box 42)
    - No. 0009, 2000-02-25; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0413 (Box 42)
    - No. 0010, 2000-03-03; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0413 (Box 42)
    - No. 0011, 2000-03-10; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0413 (Box 42)
    - No. 0012, 2000-03-17; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0414 (Box 42)
    - No. 0013, 2000-03-24; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0414 (Box 42)
    - No. 0014, 2000-03-31; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0414 (Box 42)
    - No. 0015, 2000-04-07; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0415 (Box 42)
    - No. 0016, 2000-04-14; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0415 (Box 42)
    - No. 0017, 2000-04-21; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0415 (Box 42)
    - No. 0018, 2000-04-28; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0416 (Box 42)
    - No. 0019, 2000-05-05; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0416 (Box 42)
    - No. 0020, 2000-05-12; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0416 (Box 42)
    - No. 0021, 2000-05-19; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0417 (Box 42)
    - No. 0022, 2000-05-26; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0417 (Box 42)
    - No. 0023, 2000-06-02; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0417 (Box 42)
    - No. 0024, 2000-06-09; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0418 (Box 42)
    - No. 0025, 2000-06-16; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0418 (Box 42)
    - No. 0026, 2000-06-23; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0418 (Box 42)
    - No. 0027, 2000-06-30; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0419 (Box 42)
    - No. 0028, 2000-07-07; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0419 (Box 42)
    - No. 0029, 2000-07-14; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0419 (Box 42)
    - No. 0030, 2000-07-21; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0420 (Box 42)
    - No. 0031, 2000-07-28; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0420 (Box 42)
    - No. 0032, 2000-08-04; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0420 (Box 42)
    - No. 0033, 2000-08-11; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0421 (Box 42)
    - No. 0034, 2000-08-18; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0421 (Box 42)
    - No. 0035, 2000-08-25; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0421 (Box 42)
    - No. 0036, 2000-09-01; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0422 (Box 42)
    - No. 0037, 2000-09-08; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0422 (Box 42)
    - No. 0038, 2000-09-15; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0422 (Box 42)
    - No. 0039, 2000-09-22; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0423 (Box 42)
    - No. 0040, 2000-09-29; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0423 (Box 42)
    - No. 0041, 2000-10-06; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0423 (Box 42)
    - No. 0042, 2000-10-13; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0424 (Box 42)
    - No. 0043, 2000-10-20; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0424 (Box 42)
    - No. 0044, 2000-10-27; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0424 (Box 42)
    - No. 0045, 2000-11-03; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0425 (Box 43)
    - No. 0046, 2000-11-10; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0425 (Box 43)
    - No. 0047, 2000-11-17; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0425 (Box 43)
    - No. 0048, 2000-11-24; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0426 (Box 43)
    - No. 0049, 2000-12-01; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0426 (Box 43)
    - No. 0050, 2000-12-08; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0426 (Box 43)
    - No. 0051, 2000-12-15; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0427 (Box 43)
    - No. 0052, 2000-12-22; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0427 (Box 43)
    - No. 0053, 2000-12-29; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0427 (Box 43)
  - Videorecordings, 2001
    - No. 0101, 2001-01-06; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0428 (Box 43)
    - No. 0102, 2001-01-12; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0428 (Box 43)
    - No. 0103, 2001-01-20; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0428 (Box 43)
    - No. 0104, 2001-01-26; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0429 (Box 43)
    - No. 0105, 2001-02-02; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0429 (Box 43)
    - No. 0106, 2001-02-09; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0429 (Box 43)
    - No. 0107, 2001-02-16; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0430 (Box 43)
    - No. 0108, 2001-02-23; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0430 (Box 43)
    - No. 0109, 2001-03-02; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0430 (Box 43)
    - No. 0110, 2001-03-09; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0431 (Box 43)
    - No. 0111, 2001-03-16; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0431 (Box 43)
    - No. 0112, 2001-03-23; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0431 (Box 43)
    - No. 0113, 2001-03-30; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0432 (Box 43)
    - No. 0114, 2001-04-06; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0432 (Box 43)
    - No. 0115, 2001-04-13; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0432 (Box 43)
    - No. 0116, 2001-04-20; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0433 (Box 43)
    - No. 0117, 2001-04-27; Betacam; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0433 (Box 43)